fresherjobs99.com 2011-04-01

# FresherJobs99.com

## **Website Privacy Policy**

### Policy Statement

Fresherjobs99.com adhere to the privacy protection provisions of the Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act and the information practices in the operation of this site.

### Personal Information Collection 

On our website, we collect personal information about you only when you explicitly provide it.  We protect the personal information given to us when you fill out a form. We have implemented a variety of security measures to ensure that your personal information is not lost, misused, altered, or unintentionally destroyed.

### Do we use cookies or tracking devices?

we may use cookies or tracking devices during your visit to our website. Information gathered by these technologies will disappear once you leave the website .

The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher's site(s) and across the web.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).) 

  **Further Information**  
 Website Privacy Policy  
 Contact US !
